<!--
~ Copyright 2014 Kay Stenschke
~
~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
~
~ http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
~
~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
~ limitations under the License.
-->
<idea-plugin version="2">
  <id>com.kstenschke.copypastestack</id>
  <name>Copy/Paste Stack</name>
  <vendor email="info@stenschke.com" url="">Kay Stenschke</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
      Copy/paste stack is an advanced copy history manager including a clipboard viewer.<br />
      The plugin adds a tool window of copy history items, similar to the standard copy history built-in,
      but possible to be kept persistently open and with some additional features:<br />
      <ul>
        <li>Copy/paste stack provides an unlimited long list of of copied string items, from the current and recent sessions.
            Copy/paste stack caches its content, allowing you to keep copied items for as long as needed
            (instead of limiting their availability to the current editing session).
        </li>
        <li>The full text of selected copied items can be previewed in an editable text pane.</li>
        <li>One or multiple selected items can be inserted into the editor via [ENTER] key, [SPACE] or double click,
            and can be copied back to the clipboard
        </li>
        <li>Items are automatically trimmed from surrounding whitespace.</li>
        <li>The list of copied items can be sorted chronologically or alphabetically, and grouped using color tags</li>
        <li>When pasting items back into the editor, they can be wrapped with a prefix and postfix string,
            and a delimiter when pasting multiple items at once.
        </li>
        <li>The plugin also includes a viewer for the current textual or image clipboard contents</li>
      </ul>
       <br/>Please note: This plugin is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    ]]></description>

    <version>1.1.1</version>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <ul>
        <li>1.1.1 Added refresh button for current clipboard viewer</li>
        <li>1.1.0<ul>
                <li>Added viewer for current clipboard contents (text and image)</li>
                <li>Added grouping of copy items by color tags (click refresh to update color sorting)</li>
                <li>Reduced inline changelog to previous five items, added separate full changelog</li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>1.0.9<ul>
                <li>Usability: Made preview panel always shown and resizable.</li>
                <li>Usability: Added context menu to untag button</li>
                <li>Usability: Added "Paste" and "Select all" options to preview context menu</li>
                <li>Bugfix: Activated alphabetical sort was not applied initially</li>
                <li>UI: Tag icons were 1px too small</li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>1.0.8<ul>
                <li>Added: Retina Icons</li>
                <li>Added: Link to plugin info / rating page</li>
                <li>Bugfix: Refresh didn't update items count</li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>1.0.7 Bugfix: Fixed possible null pointer exception when wiping all items</li>
    </ul><br/>
    <a href="https://github.com/kstenschke/copypastestack-plugin/blob/master/CHANGELOG.textile" target="_blank">...Read full changelog on github</a>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <!-- please see http://confluence.jetbrains.com/display/IDEADEV/Build+Number+Ranges for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="131"/>

  <!-- please see http://confluence.jetbrains.com/display/IDEADEV/Plugin+Compatibility+with+IntelliJ+Platform+Products
       on how to target different products -->
  <!-- uncomment to enable plugin in all products
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
  -->

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij" />

  <application-components />

  <project-components />

  <actions />

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="Copy/Paste" anchor="right" factoryClass="com.kstenschke.copypastestack.ToolWindowFactory">
        </toolWindow>
    </extensions>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
</idea-plugin>